Hello everyone, welcome to this live broadcast, I am the host Lidia.
This live broadcast will bring you a content about the processing of building materials.
As you all know, the real performance of building materials is divided into two parts.
The first is the physical properties of building materials, which will affect the physical effects of building materials,
including the elasticity of the fabric, etc.
It is a virtual data and virtual fabric that is obtained after the fabric measurement and fabrication.
We won't talk about this part today. If you want to know more about this part,
you can go to the link in our introduction.
The second is the physical properties of building materials.
The physical properties of building materials do not affect the physical effects of building materials,
but rather the texture of the building materials.
The physical properties of building materials include rigidity, three-dimensional, and glossiness, etc.
In other words, when we have a real piece of fabric in our hands,
what steps should we take to make this piece of fabric a more real appearance in our 3D clothing?
Today is a live broadcast with a theory topic.
Then, we all know that when it comes to fabric processing,
a basic step is divided into three steps.
The first step is our ironing.
We need to iron our fabric first.
This step is very important for the next step of a plant scan.
Then it is scanning.
Then why is it scanning and not taking pictures?
There are two very important reasons for this.
The first is because the picture of scanning and the size of the fabric of the plant are 1 to 1.
The second is because scanning pictures can basically ensure that the light received by the plant is even.
This is all impossible to take pictures.
Then this can be convenient.
After that we can use bi consequence processing.
The third step is the process of processing our fruit picture.
Then let's talk about what we need to scan.
The first thing is our scanning device.
We can use this connected scanning même directly in our office.
Do you hear everything stability?
Wait a minute, let me bring the microphone closer.
Hello, can you hear me clearly?
Okay, let's talk about our scanning device first.
We can use our integrated scanning device.
In addition, there is also a professional physical scanning device like VZoom.
This scanning device is compatible with software.
It is very convenient to scan images and calculate them through a software to generate a 3D sticker.
In today's live broadcast, we will teach you how to generate a 3D sticker in another way.
As for what a 3D sticker is, I will introduce it later.
Other scanning devices, including our tablet-type scanning device and our portable scanning device, can be scanned.
The second point is the setting of our scanning.
We need to adjust the resolution of our scanning device to 300 dpi or above.
According to our
The sound is still a little unstable.
Let's adjust it.
Let me adjust it.
Wait a minute.
Let's listen to the phone.
Yes, let's listen to it.
Let's listen to it.
Hello, can you hear it?
.
Can you hear it?
Is it better?
.
OK, OK, so let's use this channel.
Well, let's move on.
.
Then the third point is to ensure that the fabric is in the right direction and that it is in the right direction.
Then we will scan it.
After scanning, we will process the pattern.
There are four aspects to the process of the pattern.
The first is that when we scan the pattern, if there is a color difference, we need to adjust its color in the PS.
Adjust it to a more realistic color.
Then the second point is the repetition of the pattern.
That is, how to process our scan pattern into a quadrilateral.
I will explain it in a moment.
The third point is 1 to 1.
It is to ensure that the DPI of the pattern we scan and the DPI of the pattern we process in the later stage are the same.
Then the fourth point is an introduction to the concept of a plant pattern.
We can see that our pattern is on this dress.
The one on the left is a correct quadrilateral.
The one on the right does not have a quadrilateral effect.
You can see that it is a completely incorrect pattern.
So it is very important to process it into a correct quadrilateral.
Then the effect of 1 to 1.
You can see that the pattern on the left is the same as the scan pattern.
The one on the right is a modified pixel value.
So its pattern has become larger.
So we must pay attention to the consistent pixel value of this pattern.
Then the following is an introduction to a concept of our plant pattern.
Then we need the following few pictures.
It is a plant file from a Yang-Gaorong in our system fabric warehouse.
The picture on the far left is a fabric pattern that everyone is most familiar with.
Through scanning.
Then the two pictures in the middle are our hair line and
The picture on the far right is a plant pattern.
It is a
plant.
A plant made of hair.
So we get the box meat from the plant.
Then we add a plant to the box.
Then the plant расскures to our Farm Jay that when the next plant purchase will be buyed,
The plant will become a plant of theKaka wanted.
Then you can use this plant to buy raw material from the farm edge...
Which emitting the plant of the lab green just like in the channel picture picture rules.
Okay, let me show you.
First, approach to each plant in your plant.
Then the second element is what is called the plant.
Ok, so we are about to start the request for a plant on that plant.
You can see that this is a plant called Bedmium or that you can see.
This plant runs into our plant first.
Then plays its Compliance
relaxing.
through the sense of shadow to reflect the roughness of our object.
Then you can see that at the bottom of the texture in our attribute editor,
is the position of the position of our hair line sticker.
It is the effect of this blue-purple picture.
Then there is a strength below.
Then let's take a look at this strength range.
In our system, it can be set from negative 50 to positive 50.
When the strength is 0, you can see that it has no roughness at all.
When the strength is 50,
its roughness is the strongest.
You can see a change in the middle of 25.
Then the negative value is to turn the roughness into roughness.
The roughness becomes rough.
It's a reverse effect.
Then it's our hallucination picture.
The hallucination picture,
it is used to show us a 3D sticker with a real feeling of roughness in the text.
Then you can see our two dresses.
The one on the left is without a hallucination picture.
The one on the right has a hallucination picture.
We can see it in detail.
The one on the left is completely like a piece of paper.
If you zoom in,
The one on the right has a three-dimensional effect.
And this three-dimensional effect is through our hallucination picture.
That is, there is a hallucination picture below our hair sticker.
We show it through this hallucination picture.
The hallucination picture is a black and white picture like this.
Gray picture.
There are a few fingers below it.
Then we can set these fingers to achieve a different hallucination effect.
You can see it.
Our hallucination picture.
It's a gray picture.
It's the one on the left above us.
And then the one on the right.
We gave it a high silk blur in the PS.
In this way,
It can give it a more smooth effect.
Then the first one below is our hallucination degree.
What is the level of hallucination?
The level of hallucination is.
Our hallucination picture.
What is the thickness of the most prominent position?
When the level of hallucination is one,
You can see it.
That is, our white area is the highest level of hallucination.
The black area is not.
The level of hallucination is zero without a thickness.
The level of hallucination is zero.
So when our level of hallucination is one millimeter.
The white Claw.
The place of this sign.
It protrudes a height of one millimeter.
Then we change the level of hallucination to two.
You can see that it is obviously higher than the previous one.
Then the second one is our movement.
What does it mean to move?
Moving refers to our hallucination picture.
It can move one.
It can move a distance.
Then why do we set this parameter?
It's because some of our fabrics are thick.
For example, our woolen fabrics.
Then we may need to add the hallucination picture.
In a place where our plants are slightly floating.
Then we can add a positive value to it.
Then you can see this picture moving to one.
It feels a little floating.
See?
Then we look down again.
Then we see its cutting height.
Cutting height.
It corresponds to it.
Our one.
On the sticker.
One.
If we set it to 0.5.
We will cut it to a geometric shape of an area lower than 0.5.
You can see its effect.
Then here is our particle structure.
The particle structure is because our principle of this hallucination picture is in our.
Add to the horizontal grid of the hallucination picture.
To build a three-dimensional grid.
So that it can have a three-dimensional effect that protrudes out.
And the effect of our hallucination picture.
It must be in our.
Convection window.
To be able to see it.
In our 3D window.
Actual.
That.
Convection is not possible.
You have to open that.
Convection engine.
That window.
So we have to.
After opening that.
To see our one.
The effect of the hallucination picture.
And then the particle structure.
He built this grid.
If his particle structure is too big.
There will be this kind of grid.
It's too big.
And then it leads to our.
The picture created.
It doesn't look very delicate.
So we will reduce the particle structure to one.
It will be more delicate.
And because of our one.
The hallucination picture.
His one.
A.
Consumption.
He is.
It takes a lot of memory.
To render.
So I suggest you.
In the use of large areas.
When the hallucination picture.
The value of the particle structure.
Don't be lower than one.
And then the last one.
Is our continuity.
And then the continuity.
That is to say.
We put our hallucination picture.
After we put it on our object.
We put it.
After the continuity point.
His one.
The gap.
Just.
Continued.
Okay.
Next, let's take a look at our.
Highlight picture.
Is our.
Uh.
Define our object surface.
A 3D sticker with a brightness.
You can see.
I gave this cheongsam.
Above.
Uh.
Added a.
A right-hand side.
A high-light picture like this.
And then our.
If the high-lighting picture.
He is.
The black place is.
Uh.
The brightest.
And then the white part.
Is not illuminated.
So we see this black.
Uh.
Plum.
This kind of flower.
Words are on our.
The skirt.
It's now.
Present a.
A very high level of light.
A.
One.
Situation.
Ha.
One effect.
Then you can take a look.
Our one.
Strength.
With our.
is a concept of reflection intensity.
Because our intensity is below the roughness of the surface,
it refers to the strength of the roughness of the surface.
The larger the value,
the greater the roughness.
So you can see the contrast of this set.
When the roughness is 50,
the fabric looks more luminous.
Then the reflection intensity below
refers to the amount of light reflected on the fabric.
The larger the value,
the stronger the reflection effect.
So you can see in this set,
when the reflection intensity is 70,
the effect of the reflection is the strongest.
Now that we have talked about the thought process and
the concept of 3D stickers,
let's move on to today's topic.
Before we start,
I would like to talk about
different types of plant processing.
First of all,
we will talk about the color of the fabric.
Today, we will introduce a software called PixPlant.
In this software,
we will give the color of the fabric
a continuous processing
and the production of a 3D sticker.
The second is the plant of the hard flower.
There are three types of hard flower plants.
The first type is
where you already have a hard flower.
The second type is where you already have a plant.
Then we will directly use the plant in your hand
to scan it,
then continuously process it,
and generate its 3D sticker.
This we need to cooperate with
PixPlant and PixPlant.
Then the following is
if we only have a flower on our hand,
we want to express the texture of the fabric
with this flower.
How do we do it?
We can do a mechanism of compounding in our PS.
And we have a flower and a mechanism.
Then we can do a mechanism of compounding in our PS.
Then the third type is our hollow plant.
For example, the type of laser net sand.
Then how do we make it
hollow?
Then its scanning technique
and in the PS
to give it a technique of drawing a picture.
Then the last one is
our compounding material plant.
Then we need to do a layer processing
of our compounding material.
It needs to be processed in the PS.
Then this is what we
will introduce today.
Next,
we will start to introduce
the explanation of our
plastic fabric.
This is a common
hollow sand fabric.
Let's first look at its pixel.
Its resolution is 300.
Then we remember
this resolution and open our
PixPlant.
Then to load our seed file.
Load this scanned
pattern.
After loading, we change the
value of our
sample.
After that,
we can see
how we correct the
direction of our
sample.
We move this value
and then we have a preview
effect here.
Then we make sure that it is correct.
Then we move to the next step.
In this step,
it says that if there is a repeated
pattern,
it is not necessary.
So we can directly click
on this No Pattern.
Because our hollow sand is
not a particularly
regular pattern.
So it is not necessary to
select that repeated
unit.
So we click Finish and
enter our next step.
Then we can remove it
where it is not
a regular pattern.
Then we can enter
the original
parameter of our
sample.
Then it will generate such a
seamless pattern.
We can click again to generate
it and let it calculate
it again.
Then we can see its effect.
After the effect is OK,
we can enter the
generation of its 3D
color pattern.
There is no such option
in our system, so we
do not choose it directly.
Then click generate.
Then you can see that its
current shape is from our
texture to generate our
simulation pattern.
You can adjust its details and
its surface ratio.
After adjusting it,
just click OK.
Then this is a high-light
pattern generated from
our simulation pattern.
We can also choose
the brightness level.
We can choose the middle one
with the brightness level
and the low-light one.
We choose the middle one.
Then the upper right
is the effect of
generating a more
reflective effect
in the dark position
or in the bright position.
Then because in our system
the black part is reflective,
we can choose the
dark areas in source
are more reflective.
Then click OK.
After the 3D
color pattern is generated,
we can see
the effect of
our simulation pattern.
Because the foam
is not that three-dimensional,
our simulation pattern
will consume a lot of memory,
so we pass it first
and look at the
surface.
We can adjust the
smoothness of the surface
and the degree of
simulation.
We can pull it to a suitable
position so that it does not look
as rough,
which is closer to its
real effect,
and the range of the
hair line pattern below it.
Then we can adjust it.
Then we can look at
our high-light pattern.
On the high-light pattern,
there are two
adjustment values.
First, we adjust
its roughness
and smoothness.
Then we can adjust
its strength
and its contrast.
Adjust its effect a little.
After previewing
in the 3D window,
it is OK.
Then there is a reverse
direction below.
We don't need to click it
because we chose
the dark area.
Now we save this picture.
First of all,
save our simulation
pattern and then
save this picture
in our own folder
to name it.
In fact,
I talk about this software
relatively rough,
and if you want to
learn more about this software,
you can directly log in to
their official website to learn
a more detailed tutorial.
I will only talk about
some of our most common
content here
to save our
hair line pattern.
Highlighting
Finally,
we have a conservation
of our texture.
because it is actually the same as our slow-motion picture, so I directly cover the slow-motion picture that I saved before.
Then wait a moment, it may take a few seconds.
After all is saved, we now open our CLO,
and upload our project file today.
It's a bit slow, please wait a moment.
Now I will add these two pictures to this style.
First, drag our texture picture to our Fabric One.
We can zoom in to see its texture effect.
Now it is a square.
It is a continuous state.
Then we choose this branch of the tree.
Under its property editor, we open the fill color.
After opening it, let's take a look at our system.
It can directly generate a texture picture according to the effect of our texture picture to generate a texture picture.
Then let's take a look at it.
It now has a shadow effect, but it is not very obvious.
So now
let's add it.
Let's add it to the texture picture we just created.
Drag it in.
After dragging it in,
you can see that its shadow effect is stronger than just now.
Then adjust it to 50.
You can see its shadow effect.
It is a very, very, very obvious shadow effect.
After adjustment, let's see the following.
In our surface roughness, we choose our high-light picture.
Then drag in the high-light picture we just created.
Then take a look at its effect.
Then you can adjust its intensity.
After adjustment,
adjust it.
We can see that because our 3D window now is a display of a gray map.
So when we adjust these values, it doesn't make a very obvious change.
So at this time, we need to change the fill color.
We need to cancel the fill color.
Then we adjust these values again.
Reversal or something.
We can see the effect of its high-light picture.
Of course, our reverse is wrong.
So we cancel it.
You can see that I have increased its reflection intensity.
Then adjust it back.
Such an effect.
After we have adjusted it,
At this time, we click on our rendering.
In our rendering window,
To render this piece of our fabric.
You can see that it is now very.
It has a very three-dimensional effect of bubble gauze.
Here we didn't use a calligraphy.
You have to remember.
Because calligraphy is not needed for this kind of fabric.
If we use calligraphy,
It means a little bit of painting.
Okay, we can save this picture we made.
You can save it in your folder.
Then its format is ZF.
The format is AB.
After saving it,
We will find that the name of our fabric
Has become the name we just saved.
Then we can click open.
Next time we use it,
Just find this piece of fabric.
Just click open.
Okay.
The second part,
Let's introduce our one.
Hard flower fabric.
But here I choose.
In fact, it is a colored patterned fabric.
It's just that I was in the PPT.
The color of the patterned fabric.
Its one.
The principle of processing is the same as our hard flower fabric.
Is the same.
Then we find this piece of fabric.
Drag it to this piece of fabric we just built.
Then Ctrl A.
Select our board.
Apply it.
Apply it to our new fabric.
You can see that its pattern.
Now there is no continuous processing.
Then we zoom in.
Zoom in.
What do we do after zoom in?
Let's take a look.
Our.
Didn't we just display it on a pure color?
To automatically generate its line drawing?
Now let's take a look.
If we are in this kind of color.
There is a very contrasting strong color.
On the picture.
To use our system.
Automatically generate the line drawing.
Its one effect.
You can see it.
One of its black and one of its white.
The feeling of the area.
Is different.
But in fact.
Our real one.
This piece of fabric.
Its feeling.
It should be the same.
Right?
So when we encounter such a situation.
When.
We can't.
Use our system.
Automatically generate the line drawing.
Such a function.
We need.
In our.
PS.
Or PIXPLANT.
In our PIXPLANT.
To generate.
Our line drawing.
Now.
Let's go into our.
PS.
First of all.
Its one.
Four consecutive.
Do it first.
Step by step.
Let's do it first.
This picture.
A four consecutive.
We found our.
One.
Cutting tool.
Below.
A transparent cutting tool.
Then.
Enlarge our picture.
Enlarge it.
So you can see it clearly.
One of our.
One of the lines.
One.
And then we find.
The four points that are the same.
That's what you see here.
I'm all in the black box.
The upper left is a point.
Then we skip.
A loop.
In this way.
When we're dealing with it later.
You can.
Use the one in the middle.
Superlative loop.
To do our one.
Treatment.
Now.
We picked it out.
After picking it out.
We use filters.
Others.
Sub hurting.
Then.
You can have a look at our.
The image after this meeting.
He did not have a four consecutive.
You can see it.
Then we can adjust its position, distance, position of the level, and its vertical position.
Then after clicking OK, we can do a processing of a not particularly good position.
We adjust the pixels of the image to the appropriate size.
Then press the Alt key to select the right position of the pixel.
And then copy it to the position we need to process.
And then we can process our square continuous image.
This is a very detailed task.
When you are selecting, it is very important that you select the four points.
You must select the same position to find our square continuous image.
Then you can remove any unnecessary things.
Then save it now.
It is still saved in our folder.
Give it a new name.
It is a texture file of our fabric.
After saving it, we now need to do a processing of this image.
We need to use the cutting tool to cut out a small piece.
But before cutting, let's take a look at the size of this picture.
OK.
Because later we need to generate our image in our PixPlant.
Then let's take a look at the size of the image.
Width 358, height 401.
Let's record this pixel value first.
Record it.
Then after recording it, let's see that its resolution is 600.
Then click OK.
OK.
Now we are going to get rid of this part in our eyebrow drawing.
This is for the reason that we get rid of this part.
Now we get rid of this part.
This is the area where we start our character sketching.
Now we get rid of the areas.
Because we are using the base of our image,
we make it based on a pure white 허 image.
So we only get rid of this small part.
Then click OK.
Then save this small part of our drawing.
Save the object and save it directly into the seed file.
Then enter our PixPlant.
Let's create a new texture.
Enter the height and width of it into the value we just recorded, 358 and 401.
Then change our pixel value to 600.
After changing, let's add our seed file.
After adding, let's click on the next generation.
After the generation is done, you can see the effect of it.
Then you can generate it again and see it again.
After OK, we still generate our 3D sticker.
Then these two steps are the same as just now.
Let's just click OK, OK.
Enter our adjustment interface.
Let's lower the resolution of the發現 image.
It's not so rough.
We can preview it on the left.
Adjust the value of these details a little bit.
OK.
After all the adjustments, we can save our pictures.
But since we only need two pictures now,
we can directly click to save our highlights.
Then save one of its highlights.
OK, save our發現 image.
You can also save it here directly.
OK.
Save it.
After saving, let's save our slow-motion picture,
which is the picture of our text.
We will use it later.
So let's save it first.
OK.
It's a little bit lagging.
After saving it,
let's go into our Claw.
Use the pictures we just processed.
First, drag our texture image into it.
You can see that it is now a continuous effect.
Then see its發現 image.
Then drag its發現 image into it.
After dragging it in,
we can put it into details to see its effect.
We can adjust its intensity to 50.
You can see its
If you can't see it clearly,
let's fill in the color.
You can see its obvious fade,
and it is evenly changed,
which is different from the automatic production of the system just now.
Then adjust its intensity a little bit,
closer to its actual fade.
Now, let's go back to our Claw.
Choose Highlight and drag it in.
OK.
You can see it has some reflection effect now.
Right?
Then we can adjust its intensity.
Then I click on the reverse here.
Because I think its glow after the reflection,
it's closer to our real fabric.
You can click on the reverse.
When you finish the high-light picture,
and you feel that its direction is wrong,
just click on the reverse.
OK.
Now let's go to the window to see its high-light effect.
After we finish the high-light picture,
we will go to the next one.
We will go to the next one.
OK.
After this,
we will go to the next one.
OK.
After this,
we will go to the next one.
OK.
After this,
we will go to the next one.
OK.
After this,
we will go to the next one.
OK.
After this,
we will go to the next one.
OK.
After this,
we will go to the next one.
OK.
After this,
we will go to the next one.
OK.
After this,
we will go to the next one.
OK.
After this,
we will go to the next one.
OK.
After this,
we will go to the next one.
OK.
After this,
we will go to the next one.
OK.
Then after removing the color, we adjust its color interface.
Pull the three triangles of its color interface a little closer.
Let the color contrast become stronger.
We can adjust it a little bit.
This is a little too strong.
I'll make it a little weaker.
It's about this effect.
Then save it.
This is how we use PS to make our highlights.
You can also learn.
After saving it, let's use it.
We just used the highlight of PS.
Just drag it in and refresh it.
Then pull in the picture of the highlight we just made with PS.
After pulling it in, we can render it and see its effect.
You can also use PS to make your highlights.
Press the shutter button on your smartphone, and press the shutter button on your phone.
This will make the highlight on your phone look brighter.
It's said that the highlights of PS are more great when you use PS than when you use PS.
I'm going to add some highlights.
You can add highlights and shadows depending on your preference.
And then we can add highlights.
I'm going to add highlights.
This is an example of how to create a highlight.
I'm going to show you how to create a highlight.
This is just a highlight.
we can turn off the rendering.
Next, let's talk about
a hard drawing.
When we have a drawing,
how do we express
the texture of a real plant?
Because we all know that
if there is only one drawing,
let's pull it in first and take a look.
If we only have one drawing,
let's zoom in and see
if it has a plant texture.
Here we have several ways.
The first way is
to use the hair line sticker.
The hair line sticker
has a box.
We can find the corresponding
hair line sticker
in the box.
Let's zoom in and see
how it works.
Now we have
the texture.
Of course, if we have
a base material in our hand,
we need to print the flower
on the base material.
Then we can also use
the texture we just created
to match
the hard drawing.
You can see
that I have
both the hard drawing
and the texture
in the PS.
After that,
we can define
the pattern
in the texture.
After that,
we can add
a layer
and unlock it.
After unlocking it,
we can place the layer
on the bottom.
The flower is printed on the top,
so we place the layer on the bottom.
Then we fill the blank layer
with the texture we just defined.
After filling it,
we select the layer
and switch the mode
to the top.
We switch it to a
flat bottom mode.
Then we can see
that we have
a hard-painted
texture.
Now,
let's save the texture
and select the JPG
format.
Save it
and
click OK.
Now,
let's replace
the picture
we just created.
Let's see
the picture
we just created.
We can see
the texture
we just created.
The texture of the plant
is very important.
When we think
the texture of the plant
is not strong enough,
we can add the picture
and make it stronger.
We can also
add the highlight picture.
This way,
we can use
an ordinary flower
to make
the texture
more realistic.
Now,
let's talk about
the processing of
the texture.
Let's download
a new project file.
This example is
a demonstration
in my previous PPT.
Now,
let's drag
the picture
we just created
into the project.
When we drag the picture,
we can see
the texture
is white.
When we drag the picture
into the project,
the yellow color
looks like
a yellow paper.
Yes,
it's a light color.
Now,
we need to
add a paper.
Because our scanner
is white,
it will be very inconvenient
to drag the picture
into the project.
We recommend
you to choose a color
that is close to
your skin color.
Let's use
the color
that is close to
your skin color.
Now,
we can
drag the picture
into the project.
Let's drag
the picture
into the project.
Let's drag
the picture
into the project.
Now,
we can drag
the picture
into the project.
We can drag
the picture
into the project.
Now,
the picture
will be
very clear.
Now,
we can drag
the picture
into the project.
Now,
You can see that it now has this kind of hollow effect, and the bottom is connected.
Let's turn on our rendering to see its effect.
You can see its rendering effect now.
Wait a moment.
You can see that it now has no three-dimensional effect at all.
It looks like a piece of paper.
So how do we make it three-dimensional?
As I mentioned earlier, we need to add a
We need to add a three-dimensional effect in order to make it more realistic.
So how do we make it three-dimensional?
In our PS, we select all the pixels in this layer.
Then fill it with white.
After filling all the pixels with white, cancel the selection.
Then add a black layer.
Add this black layer to the new layer.
Fill it in.
After filling it in, drag it to the bottom of our white texture layer.
Then merge these two layers together.
Do you remember?
In our PS, it is a gray layer.
The white layer is the highest level of saturation.
The black layer is the lowest level of saturation.
So we need to make it a higher level of saturation.
To make it more uniform and more three-dimensional.
Adjust the radius of the higher level of saturation to about 4.5.
About 4.5.
OK.
It's done.
It looks like this.
Let's save it.
Save it as a JPEG image.
Rename it.
OK.
Now let's switch to our CLO software.
Then add our simulation image.
OK.
Let's see how it works.
After adding it, let's zoom in and see.
These settings we added are default settings for our simulation image.
You can see that its particle diameter is 4.
And the saturation is 3.
It's very rough.
So it must be wrong.
Then we change its particle diameter to 1.
And then change the saturation to 1.5.
Then we zoom in again.
This is the result .
As you can see, our simulation image has a very high level of noise.
And our result can't be bad.
Because the simulation image consumes a lot of our memory.
So when it's saturated,
it's gonna be slower than normal material if you have a simulation image.
Ok.
I found that there's a white border here.
Then I change its movement distance to "-1", and then render it again.
Now the edge of the white lace is gone.
This is the technique of making a three-dimensional water-coloured lace.
If you have any questions, please feel free to ask in the comments.
The effect of this dress is done.
Let's move on to the next style.
Open the project file, and this is the final result.
This is a shirt.
Now I want to add a pattern to the white fabric area.
The pattern has a sand-like texture at the bottom,
and there is a shiny dot at the top.
It is made of two different materials.
This is how it looks when we scan the pattern and add it directly after doing a four-way sequence.
This effect is definitely wrong, because it has a sense of transparency.
So let's do it here.
Let's do it here.
We can do a processing of it.
When we process it, we take out this non-transparent dot,
and then do a four-way sequence.
Then we can take out the pattern and do it again.
The method is the same as the previous one.
But here I stole a wool.
Because the effect of the bottom sand is very close to the black snow-white fabric in our system.
So I directly pull in a snow-white fabric.
Then change its color to black.
After confirming it, increase its transparency a little bit.
Adjust it to a real effect that is close to it.
Then I paste the pattern in advance.
Increase as a sticker.
Then add it in.
This way, we use the fabric and the sticker to make a two-layer texture different.
Its bottom is transparent now, but its spot is not transparent.
Then we repeat its pattern.
After we repeat it, we can select the type of the sticker.
Choose this flashing effect.
Then we can copy the sticker to the symmetrical board.
Then we copy and paste the sticker to the other board.
It will automatically fill the board.
It's pasted directly.
Now we have a composite material with a thin sand base with a dot on it.
We can check the effect at the window.
We are almost done with today's video.
We still have a lot of time left.
But I would like to see if there are any questions.
If there are no questions, we will...
Any questions?
Let me take a look.
Where is the problem?
No problem.
It's over at nine o'clock.
I know.
Now let's move on to the next step.
It's the egg-picking step.
We want to make a three-dimensional embroidery sticker.
Let's insert one of our...
Our costume.
Then we insert our Feifei.
And then we simulate it.
And now we're going to add one of our...
One of the egg-picking documents.
Add it.
It's a PNG picture.
Then we add it as a sticker.
Add it to our costume.
Above.
Okay, let's put it in the position of our chest, move it, and now let's open our rendering to see its texture effect of just adding a sticker.
Okay, you can see that it is now a sticker with no three-dimensional effect.
Now, how should we make a three-dimensional sticker for it?
I believe you have already guessed it through the explanation just now.
We should do it with our
next step.
Then, we will merge these two pictures into one.
After merging, we will blur the filter.
Then, we will adjust the radius to a 5.
It's a bit too high.
2, right?
2.
Okay, it's about this effect.
Then, we will save it.
Okay.
Save it.
Okay, after saving it, we will add an illusion picture on it.
It's this picture just now.
Add it to our illusion picture.
Okay, after adding it, we will change its level of illusion to 1.5.
For example, we will adjust it to 1.
Then, we will simulate it.
Oh, no.
We will render it.
Okay, now you can see that it has a three-dimensional effect.
Okay.
Is it much more three-dimensional than just now?
This is our egg-cutting part.
Actually, the method is the same.
Why should we put it in the egg-cutting part?
Because it is not a plant.
It is an effect of a sticker.
So, I put it in an egg-cutting part.
But the principle is the same.
In our sticker side, it can also increase our illusion picture.
It shows our three-dimensional sense, okay?
Let me have a look.
How to do the first grid.
What you said is that the first grid is the highest.
The first grid is the highest.
It's very low.
If you look at the first grid, the first grid is the highest.
How do you do this?
The first grid is the highest.
What you said is the highest.
Are you talking about how to do quadruple-continuity?
Quadruple-continuity, right?
Then I'll...
Oh, okay.
Let's take a look at quadruple-continuity.
Let's open our PS.
Join our quadruple-continuity today.
It should be this picture.
After joining,
we choose our transparent cutting tool.
To choose a continuous pattern.
Let's zoom in a little bit.
Let's choose four points.
That is, I can find this black grid.
This point on the top left.
Then to this point.
Then select these four points.
After selecting it,
I chose the wrong one.
Go back.
Black grid.
Top left.
Four points on the top left.
Of course, to the bottom.
We need to go over a pattern.
Cross a circle.
Then click this.
Then look at its position on the filter side.
Okay, confirm.
You can see that there is a gap here now.
There is a gap here.
Can you see?
If it doesn't do a particularly good continuous cutting now,
to select a position that needs to be copied.
For example, I press the Alt key to select this position
and then fill it in.
In this way, we can get a solution for the position of this pin.
It's probably a principle like this.
Are there any other questions?
If you feel that some of the previous operations are too fast and you don't understand them,
you can watch the replay.
We will play the replay next week.
How to make a pvc laser fabric?
The pvc laser fabric can be made.
We need to make the pvc laser fabric.
I have made the pvc laser fabric before.
As long as the pvc laser fabric has the effect of the pvc laser fabric,
and the pvc laser fabric is added,
you can make the pvc laser fabric.
There is a property type here.
We can change the pvc laser fabric to a metal option.
In this way, the material of our pvc laser fabric
will have a better sense of reflection.
The pvc laser fabric and pvc laser fabric
In fact, in the system,
there may be no comparison for this part for the time being.
That is to say,
you can choose one and then you can achieve such an effect operation.
But we can actually use some of them in the pvc laser
to deal with some special colors.
The texture of a sticker,
and then the texture of the sticker to increase some,
for example, the effect of metal.
Or some other effects.
That is, we can focus on special fabric, special analysis.
That is, after we analyze a specific fabric,
Anyway, I have done something similar before.
And the effect is still okay.
It can achieve the feeling of the pvc laser you are talking about.
Although there is no such effect in the system to choose it.
It needs some skills.
That is a very advanced content.
So I'm not ready today.
Next is a pig-patterned embroidery.
Pig-patterned embroidery.
Pig-patterned embroidery, isn't it?
Pig-patterned embroidery, in fact,
like this kind of embroidery,
is what you talk about these embroidery and what,
in fact, its principle is that
we need to scan this pattern itself.
Or, like pig-patterned embroidery,
if it can't scan, we can take pictures.
When taking pictures, you should pay attention to our one.
Take a picture.
so that the light can be more even,
and then we can process our pattern 1 to 1,
and then add it to our system.
But in the case of Zhu Pin Xiu,
its three-dimensional effect will be a little more complicated.
We will record this problem later,
if there is an egg-picking part,
I will show you again.
After all, this is indeed a bit difficult.
Does the pattern of the embroidery flower have to have a pattern?
Yes, our embroidery flower must have a pattern.
Zhu Pin Xiu,
someone help me answer, right?
Then,
how to adjust the size of the pattern?
The size of the pattern,
are you talking about the size of our fabric pattern?
We can adjust it directly with our pattern editor.
Yes,
yes,
so we can adjust it directly with our pattern editor.
Then,
how do we adjust the size of our pattern?
How do we adjust it after we can adjust the size?
I don't understand this problem,
what do you mean?
Use the pattern,
to paste diamonds,
what kind of problem?
I have not heard of that,
how to make Zhu Pin Xiu difficult.
隐形眼镜拉链怎么做?
隐形眼镜拉链是什么?
这个问题太诡异了。
6.0的纹理编辑器有什么新功能吗?
这个还需要大家再期待一下。
6.0我也还没有用上。
发现贴图和纹理的区别是什么?
这个区别很大的。
纹理是制作服装纹理的一个基本图。
也就是说你拿到一块面料,
你去把它进行一个扫描,
那这个扫描的图片也就是你面料的纹理图。
而我们的发现贴图,
它是那种蓝紫色的一个图片,
它是去体现我们纹理上的一个机理感的一个3D贴图,
是在我们纹理图的下方去进行一个添加的。
隐形拉链,哦,隐形拉链。
隐形拉链的话,我们一般就直接就不做了,
就直接把它缝起来,
然后你做一个头,
做一个隐形拉链的头,
把它用附件的形式,
粘在那个隐形拉链的头的那个位置就OK了。
扫描那个机器就是打印,
对对对,扫描机器就是打印店那种一体机。
贴钻石化立体效果,
有人帮我再回答是吗?
感谢你啊,感谢你。
还有两分钟,直播就要结束了,
大家还有什么问题吗?
我们的面料测量仪是什么原理?
我们的面料测量仪,
它是通过,怎么说呢,
就是它是去对我们的面料的一些物理的属性,
比如说拉伸性啊,旋垂性啊,去进行一个测试,
然后我们会记录下一些数据嘛,
然后把这些数据输入到我们的电脑当中,
就是我们的软件的那个面料计算的这么一个模式,
可以看到这有个面料计算模式,
然后输入进去之后,
我们有一套算法对这些数据进行处理,
然后处理成我们的一个电子面料。
置换图的位置有扣眼渲染的时候就没有了。
这个问题,置换图的位置在有扣眼渲染的时候就没有了。
我对这个问题不是很清晰,
你可以再描述的清晰一点吗?
下节课是下下周的周五晚上8点。
关注我们的公众号。
扭折,扭折不是今天的一个授课内容,
所以我们就不在这里进行解答了。
到时候我们其他的一个主题直播可以来为大家介绍。
刺绣图加黑底是吧?
有人在帮我解答,太感谢你们了。
今天时间是不是到点了?
置换图一定要加黑底这个问题问得好啊。
为什么要加黑底?
因为我们的黑色是没有置换效果。
就是它的置换程度为0的一个效果。
所以说如果你上面只有部分立体的话,
因为我们的黑色是没有置换效果。
If we only have some parts that need to be white or gray, then our map will be black.
Okay, okay, we're going to end the broadcast today.
It's already past one o'clock.
The teacher is about to get off work.
See you next week.
If you have any questions, you can watch our replay, okay?
Bye bye, everyone.
See you next week.
Stop, right?
Okay, stop.